https://www.midatlanticpackaging.com/privacy-policy/

Menu
BagsPaper BagsPaper Shopping BagsDecorative Paper Shopping BagsGourmet & SOS Paper BagsEuro Tote BagsPaper Merchandise BagsPlastic BagsFrosted Shopping BagsMulti-Purpose Plastic Bags (T-Shirt Bags)Reusable BagsPouch BagsBoxesApparel BoxesGable BoxesGiftware BoxesLock-Corner BoxesJewelry BoxesJewelry Boxes with CottonJewelry Boxes with Peachboard Inserts1 Piece Jewelry BoxAccessories for Jewerly BoxesGift Card BoxesPouch and Pillow BoxesFlower BoxesDecorative Corrugated BoxesFood & Gourmet BoxesDecorative Holiday & Christmas BoxesMagnetic Folding Ceco BoxesFood & GourmetFood & Gourmet BagsFood & Gourmet Paper BagsPlastic Food & Gourmet BagsReusable BagsFood Packaging & Gourmet BoxesBakery & Cupcake BoxesCandy BoxesDeli & Lunch BoxesGable BoxesWine BoxesOlive Oil & Vinegar BoxesTake Out Containers & BoxesTulip BoxesMacaron Boxes & TraysTwist TiesTwist Tie RollsSatin Twist Tie BowsTwist TiesMetallic Twist Tie BowsGrosgrain Twist Tie BowsTwine & CordFood Grade Tissue PaperDry Wax Tissue PaperBakery Tissue PaperBakery Tissue SheetsDeli Tissue PaperFood Service Printed Tissue PaperKiss Waxed Tissue PaperMenu Tissue Paper UnwaxedDisposable CupsWine PackagingWine BagsWine BoxesDecorative & Holiday Wine BagsDecorative Holiday & Christmas BoxesGift Basket SuppliesCello & Gift Basket BagsEveryday Printed Cello BagsSpecial Occasion Printed Cello BagsHoliday & Christmas Printed Cello BagsGift Basket BagsCello RollsAll Occasion Printed Cello RollsSpecial Occasion Printed Cello RollsChristmas Printed Cello RollsClear Cello RollsGift Basket EquipmentGlue Dots, Stickers Doos & TiesMylarGift Basket Shred / FillerShrink Wrap Bags For Gift BasketsShrink Wrap FilmPerfect BowsGift CardsEmbossed SealsGift WrapWrapping PaperEveryday Gift WrapSolid Color Gift WrapFeminine Gift WrapMasculine Gift WrapBaby Gift WrapKids Birthday-Celebration Gift WrapWedding Gift WrapJewelers Roll Gift WrapChristmas Gift WrapValentine's Day Gift WrapCutter Boxes - Special Value Gift WrapPaper CuttersLabels & TagsGift CardsProduct LabelsPricing Guns, Labels & InkProduct TagsTach-It Guns, Needles & BarbsEmbossed SealsRibbons & BowsGift BowsPerfect BowsPom BowsPull BowsStar BowsRibbon RackRibbon SlitterRibbonsTwist TiesTwine & CordPrinted RibbonWired RibbonCurling RibbonDecorative CordsGrosgrain RibbonSplendorette RibbonSatin RibbonSimply Sheer RibbonStretch LoopsTaffeta RibbonTulle RibbonWraphia RibbonRibbon YarnShipping SuppliesBubble WrapReverse Tuck CartonsCorrugated ProductsBoxesCorrugated MailersFiller PaperPaper RollsPacking PeanutsPacking Tissue PaperShipping Mailers and EnvelopesShipping Packaging TapeTissue PaperKraft & White Tissue PaperKraft Tissue PaperWhite Tissue PaperColored Tissue Paper15 x 20 Colored Tissue Paper20 x 30 Colored Tissue Paper20 x 30 Colored Tissue Paper Flat PackedMini Packs of Colored Tissue PaperPrinted Tissue PaperEveryday Printed Tissue PaperMetalized Printed Tissue PaperHot Spots Printed Tissue PaperHoliday & Christmas Printed Tissue PaperGingham Tissue PaperGemstone Color Tissue PaperFloral Tissue PaperEmbossed Printed Tissue PaperReflections Printed Tissue PaperPearlesence Color Tissue PaperFood Grade Tissue PaperDry Wax Tissue PaperBakery Tissue PaperBakery Tissue SheetsDeli Tissue PaperFood Service Printed Tissue PaperKiss Waxed Tissue PaperMenu Tissue Paper UnwaxedFloral Tissue PaperTissue Paper AssortmentsFlorist Foil RollsNEW! TissueCustom Hot Stamped Paper BagsHot Stamped Plastic BagsInk Printed Plastic BagsPost Printed Ink ShoppersFull Made to Order Ink Printed ShoppersHot Stamped BoxesCustom Printed Tissue PaperProprietary Products
Account
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
SECTION 1 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?
When you purchase something from our store, midatlanticpackaging.com, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address.
When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.
Email marketing: In an effort to better serve you we occasionally send email about specials and products by email. At any time you can choose to remove your name from this list by opting out. Naturally, you can choose subscribe again anytime in the future.
SECTION 2 - CONSENT
How do you get my consent?
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.
If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.
How do I withdraw my consent?
If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at contact@midatlanticpackaging.com or mailing us at: Mid-Atlantic Packaging 14 Starlifter Avenue, Dover, DE, 19901, United States
SECTION 3 - DISCLOSURE
We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.
SECTION 4 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICES
Mid-Atlantic Packaging is deeply committed to protecting the privacy of those that use our web-site and we take every precaution to ensure that your information is kept secure and confidential. The information collected is solely used by Mid-Atlantic Packaging and is not shared, or sold, to other third party organizations.
In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.
However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.
For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.
Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.
Links
When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.
SECTION 5 - SECURITY
To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.
If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) using up to 256-bit encryption and three encryption algorithms, RSA, DSA, and ECC, within the same SSL certificate.
Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we take every precaution to secure your information by implementing additional generally accepted industry standards.
COOKIES
Cookies are small text files that are stored by a web browser on a web-site user’s computer. Cookies will not harm your computer and, in fact, provide information that helps us improve your shopping experience on the Mid-Atlantic Packaging website.
Here is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.
HubSpot's tracking code sets the following cookies:
__hstc
The main cookie for tracking visitors. It contains: the domain, utk (see below), initial timestamp (first visit), last timestamp (last visit), current timestamp (this visit), and session number (increments for each subsequent session)
(Expires: 2 years)
hubspotutk
This cookie is used for to keep track of a visitor's identity. This cookie is passed to HubSpot on form submission and used when deduplicating contacts.
(Expires: 10 years)
__hssc
Cookie for keeping track of sessions. This is used to determine if we should increment the session number and timestamps in the __hstc cookie. It contains: the domain, viewCount (increments each pageView in a session), session start timestamp.
(Expires: 30 min)
__hssrc
Whenever HubSpot changes the session cookie, this cookie is also set. We set it simply to the value "1", and use it to determine if the user has restarted their browser. If this cookie does not exist when we manage cookies, we assume it is a new session.
(Expires: None. Session cookie)
__hs_opt_out
This cookie is used by the opt-in privacy policy to remember not to ask the user to accept cookies again. This cookie is set when you give users the choice to opt out of cookies.
(Expires: 2 years)
__hs_do_not_track
This cookie is set when you give users the choice to opt out of cookies and they choose to do so. It disables tracking and personalization.
(Expires: 2 years)
__hs_testcookie
This cookie used to test whether the visitor has support for cookies enabled.
(Expires: Session cookie)
hsPagesViewedThisSession
This cookie used to keep track of page views in a session.
(Expires: Session cookie)
hsfirstvisit
This cookie used to keep track of a user's first visit.
(Expires: 10 years)
Magento's tracking code sets the following cookies:
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FORM_KEY
Stores form key used by page cache functionality.
FRONTEND
Your session ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wish List.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wish List.
Google Analytics' tracking code sets the following cookies:
_utma
Distinguishes users and sessions.
_utmb
Determines new sessions/visits.
_utmc
Determines if the user was in a new session/visit.
_utmz
Stores the traffic source or campaign that explains how the user reached your site.
SECTION 6 - AGE OF CONSENT
By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.
SECTION 8 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.
If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.
QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION
If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at contact@midatlanticpackaging.com or by mail at Mid-Atlantic Packaging [Re: Privacy Compliance Officer] [14 Starlifter Avenue, Dover, DE, 19901, United States]
Slava Yurthev Copyright
Copyright © 2017 MidAtlantic Packaging. All rights reserved.
